

Contact

& +48 725 673 591

■ wojciech.stancel@gmail.com

LinkedIn

Github Repository

Technical Skills

- HTML
- Python
- CSS
- Pycharm
- JavaScript
- Postgresql
- Sass
- SQL
- React (Vite,
- Django
- Next)
- Nginx
- Gulp
- Git
- SEO
- Slack
- Tailwind
- Visual Studio
 Code

Soft Skills

- Analytical thinking and problem solving
- Big motivation to learn and self development
- Perfect communication

Languages

- Polish- native
- English- B2

WOJCIECH STANCEL

Junior Frontend Developer



I have spent over a year learning programming skills. Over three years of experience in previous jobs have given me perfect social, communication and problem solving skills. Please have a look at my personal portfolio to get information about all my projects.

IT PROJECTS

My website - portfolio

Wojciech-Stancel.pl

Link to repository: Portfolio-Website-Github

My website for clients

CodeCr8ive.pl

Link to repository: <u>CodeCr8ive-Github</u>

Memory Game (Next.js)

Memorygame.site

Link to repository: Memory-Game-Github

React Project

Application connected with Realtime Database on Firebase

Live view: YourNotes

Link to repository: YourNotes-Github

E-Shop (Vite.js)

Application is still under development Link to repository: <u>E-Shop-Github</u>

Website for Photographer

Live view: FotoStory

Link to repository: FotoStory-Github

Real Estate Office Website - fullstack project

Django, Postgresql, Bootstrap, Nginx

Live view: WSRealEstate

Link to repository: <u>WSRealEstate-Github</u>

WORK EXPERIENCE

Freelancing

Frontend Developer | 10.2023 - now

Travel Ready Center worker

Scandinavian Airlines | 7.2021 - 11.2022

· verification of entry documents

Contact

& +48 725 673 591

wojciech.stancel@gmail.com

Course in progress

Understand React (Zrozumieć React)

A course from the authors of the youtube channel How to start programming?

WOJCIECH STANCEL





WORK EXPERIENCE

Passenger service agent

Welcome Airport Services | 12.2018 - 6.2022

In this job I developed skills such as communication, quick decision-making and teamwork. Every day I served hundreds of passengers from all over the world, many times facing difficult and unpredictable situations. My responsibilities included.

- · coordination of the check-in and boarding process
- · responsibility for compliance with airline procedures
- onboarding of new employees
- preparation of reports

EDUCATION

Python

Orange Foundation Coding school | 12.2022-06.2023

- Python basic and intermediate
- Software testing and TDD
- Backend technologies

Link to certificate: Python Certificate

Aviation

War Studies University | Master degree | 2018-2020

• Civil Aviation Safety Management